ED
OH!!!
This is a direct ground making
It's a quick R. Fujimots.
No, wow!
Eh, wow, wow, wow!
Prince is amazing! Seriously, amazing!
Oryoumae!
Oh, this is seriously amazing!
Mr. Seta, what happened?
Mr. Seta!
What?
Thank you for your hard work.
This is it.
This is the...
This is the audience store.
Good work, sir.
I'll do three legs from two.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, I put this on.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much.
I put it right there.
Please.
Mr. Younosi?
I'm Yunoshi. Pleased to meet you.
I'm Sakura Seta from the Batten Girls Club.
Nice to meet you.
I see you're watching me here.
Yes.
Which game is your favorite?
Well, I'm trying to play Apex professionally.
You're playing?
Yeah.
That's about it.
I like it, and then we all talk about it a little bit. I'm sure you'll like it and get everyone to fluff it up a bit.
Nice to meet you.
Let's hear you say one thing.
I don't like it.
Al Savino.
The O'Bryan Studio is here.
He's stepping so well.
And now, here we are on stage.
On the theme of "D-Sports", let's experience D-Sports!
R Kujimoto and Tate-Sakura are going to have a showdown with our guest princesses.
R Kujimoto and Tetsusakura are going to have a showdown with our guest princesses!
I hope you can see how much fun they are having.
We hope you will enjoy watching them have fun!
It's time to share the fun with you!
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Let's have our guests join us right away!
Mr. R. Kujimoto, Mr. Tate-Sakura, Roguraman,
Mr. Daisho, and Mr. Minoshi.
Rejito.
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Oh, yes, yes, yes
that one
excuse me for disturbing you
I'm looking forward to working with you.
please.
I'm Vegeta.
Shut up.
Wow!
Hey, R Fujimoto.
It's Vegeta.
Hey, Fujimoto.
That's right.
My classmate R. Fujimoto is now...
No, he's not.
He's Prince Vegeta, Planet Saiyan. Planet Saiya, Prince Vegeta.
That earthly acquaintance of yours, R. Fujimoto.
Over here.
He's dead.
Dead.
If he's dead, it's going to be very difficult for us to proceed.
I'm gonna set off some fireworks.
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much.
Prince, I'm sorry you had to come all the way here.
R. Fujimoto's.
It's Vegeta.
Amazing.
I don't care how many times I hear it.
Shut up, you son of a bitch!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I got excited.
I'm sorry.
Okay, Mr. Vegeta.
Yes?
Mr. Seta.
Yes, I'm Sakura Seta, the winner of the Valiten Award.
Pleased to meet you.
Tseta Sakura
Yes, thank you very much.
I'm Nodogura, winner of the Crazy Rakoo Award!
I'm Nodogura, the Crazy Luck Award winner.
I'm Meshikure, nice to meet you.
I'm Mameshikure, nice to meet you.
Memsikre. - Memsikre.
Memsikre.
Pleased to meet you.
Ippeitan Junta.
I play streaming, I have this kind of więcej.
Yo, I'm a must! Yo, must
please give me a hand
Cute.
Thank you very much.
Today we are going to experience the game with all of you.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you know what game we're going to play today, Set-san? The game we're going to play today is...
What is it?
Um...
Super Pro Ray?
On the NES?
The game I'm playing.
I'm afraid I'm a little behind in my preparations.
Do you know it?
I've only seen it introduced in the Nintendo Direct.
I've never seen you play it.
I know of it, but I've never played it.
That's what I mean.
Mr. Matari, please tell us about today's game.
Today's game is...
A very popular NINTENDO Switch game!
Super Nodage World and
Yes, sir.
Do you know this game?
Well, it's R. Fujimoto's
Egita.
Our company's, our company's...
Yes, sir.
Our comedian...
Mr. Vegeta and his comedian Noda Crystal supervised the project.
And they made it through crowdfunding.
I see.
Well, it's a party game that mixes various games
Party game mixed with various games.
It's an assortment of shitty games, isn't it?
Yes, well, please choose your words.
I'm trying very hard to choose the right words.
We'll have a game showdown... We have a game showdown of "What's it like to be a professional gamer?
and see what it's like to be a professional gamer.
We hope that you will be able to experience these things with us.
It's a super nodage world!
I think our seats are this way.
Only Dora will be seated a little lower.
Can I sit next to you, Seta? This one.
This one, next to this one. Can you sit next to this one? Look, look, look, look.
You've got quite a presence.
Take off the shoulder pads. Are they called shoulder pads?
They're not shoulder pads.
It's a flattop.
Flatulence.
Okay, well, can I see the game screen for a second?
Would you like to see how to play just to be sure?
Maybe, but I don't know much about it.
Yes, I don't know anything about this game even if I look at the rules.
Don't tell me.
That's ridiculous. No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I control this Decca girl.
What? You're the Glock sock that controls this Decca girl, right?
Yeah, that's right.
And then we'll know the rest when we do it.
Yes, the rest is a game of doing!
And when you bump into her, her face gets bigger and bigger...
And then you say, "Oh, and then...
That's what I'm supposed to say.
I don't care if it's said with a feeling.
First of all, you know, once...
If it's faster to do it once
Is it faster to do it than to practice it?
It doesn't say what to do
You should do it one more time.
I don't know what the conditions are, but if you try it, you'll understand.
I understand. I understand.
There are no rules in fighting.
Just remember, when you take the puck, the kid gets smaller.
Prince, hand, hand.
What the hell?
Prince, something's a bit...
My robe.
This one's swarming.
It's a swarm.
Gondoliers are small.
They swarm.
I took them off.
You mean you're gonna do it right?
I'll give you 20.
That's right.
That's right. So...
Okay, I'll do it now.
Green Decca-chan is the prince.
That's right.
Yellow Decca is Mr. Seta
And blue Decca is Mr. Inoi
And Chris Noda...
Um...
Dogura
Mr. Dogura
Okay, let's go!
Go, go, go!
That's a lot of pressure back there.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's coming around this way.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Don't get hit.
Don't hit the ball.
You're not supposed to hit the ball.
And when the block breaker is over, it's clear!
I don't remember that character.
I don't remember such a character in Dragon Ball. I don't remember there being a character like that in Dragon Ball.
But then again, we're all involved in the game.
I'm sure you're avoiding them well.
If you press the red button
There are various effects of items.
This time, speed up!
It speeds up the game a little bit.
Oh, this is definitely not going to work, is it?
This is a win.
Yes, sir.
I think we can do it, guys.
It's getting weird.
Yes, sir.
That's fine.
You're free to go.
Hey...
You've come all this way.
No, you see, Mr. Fujimoto...
Oh, there's Vegeta!
Vegeta's here!
Isn't it great?
I don't know... but we're making good progress.
In the latter half of the game, when the red color is solidified, the game moves quickly, so be careful.
There are a lot of items.
Yes, it's still speeding up.
Oh, I see, it speeds up.
But when I look at this, everyone is moving to the same position.
But when you look at this, everyone is moving to the same position, and when they get to the same position, you can hit or miss by a slight difference.
I see.
I hope you enjoy that.
If you don't touch it, you won't know what's going on.
When one person touches it, the gameplay changes dramatically.
What do you mean?
Yes, not yet.
It's easy to understand that it's Noda-san.
If the sound collapses all at once, it speeds up even more!
The back disappears, speed up, speed up, speed up! Back disappears, speeds up, speeds up.
Kill?
Yes. Two more bullets.
Oh, this is tough.
And speed up.
I'll be there.
And this is a face pack.
When you take out the face pack, the count goes down.
I see what you mean.
That's right. Face packs have an advantage.
The face pack has the advantage.
I hit it.
This is not the end.
We're going to start with one bigger pack.
Inside is advantageous. And we're clear.
Do you understand? I think I understand it now.
Oh, that's easy to understand.
I've been there. I've been there before. I've seen it before.
Of course.
I'm going inside the big one.
It's a standard practice to get inside the big ones.
I see.
I see. So it won't hit at all?
You'll never hit anything.
I see.
And after three or four times, the big one gets so big that it fills up the screen and that's the end of it.
So you hid it and took the screen pack and went inside by yourself? Kouraki
Oh, my God!
It's Kouraki! It's Yuki Yuki from Gundam!
Oh, what a surprise!
It's me, Egita!
He'll do anything for you if you ask him.
I told you, Yuki Yuki Koura.
Thank goodness for that.
Let's move on to the next stage.
I'll take you to the next stage.
Next stage? We'll go to the next stage.
But somehow I think we're all ready for this. Well, but somehow I think we can all afford it now, can't we?
Okay, I'll be back.
I guess we can't go over the block.
But there's probably a safe area.
I think there's a safe area.
Let's speed up.
Is this plate thing down there always going to be in a reflective position?
Yeah.
That's great.
Peketan No, you're right.
Peketan. Um...
Peketan, up...
This Mr. Noda Crystal doesn't move at all, because he's found a strategy.
You've found a strategy, right?
And you take this one, you take this one.
And then you take this one, and it goes into someone else's body.
How's that?
Come on, all at once, all at once, all at once.
Got it?
Who? Who hit it?
Okay, here we go.
If you're not careful, it'll hit you.
Oh, I see. If you get hit, you can disable the face mask.
If you hit it, it'll make you look bigger.
You know what I'm talking about.
You know, the smaller face pack of the guy who just got his face pack?
Yes, yes.
It's very, very big. It's very big.
I'm going in.
Oh, and there's one left.
What's it gonna be?
We're gonna hit it.
Oh, it's a big one.
What happens now?
It's gonna be like this, right? This is how it's gonna be, right?
Not yet.
Oh, and then they're gone.
When you're the biggest, you're gone.
Well, one down.
Hey, Mr. Yuno, how do you feel now?
Grandpa.
Are you still frustrated?
Oh, ah...
Ah... ah... ah...
Grandpa.
You're piling it up.
Last one's piled up.
Oh!
Noda, Noda, that's a great game.
What do you think? Pro.
It's okay.
It's OK.
It's a pretty interesting game.
It didn't work at all.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're good at finding the other side.
Clear the stage.
Sakura, you're good, too.
No, no, no, you're great, Futa-san.
You're amazing!
You're so amazing!
Amazing.
Really.
So, what should we do with this one?
Shall we decide to finish it? Which one of you is...
Oh, are we going to continue this together? Oh, I wonder if this is going to continue with two more people.
Maybe next time it'll be just the two of us.
Is it okay if we go to the clear stage then?
Yes, I'll go.
The finals.
We can't lose.
I'll do my best.
Yes, two.
They look so strong!
Noda. Noda, you look super strong.
Oh, you can't get out?
Oh, I see.
Oh, get out.
Then it's gonna be tough if it comes in.
It's tough when they come in.
I wish this was a game.
The moment they come in, you have to get out.
You'd better get out. You'd better get out.
But can we go up there?
Oh, it's pretty bad.
Ahh...
That's good.
I don't think we can get out of here, huh?
Anti-anti, anti-anti.
Can we get out of here? Can we get out of here?
Oh, no.
This is a little bit...
I still don't get it.
Okay, okay, okay. Barrier, barrier, barrier.
Still not picking up.
Operation Barrier.
Barrier.
It's invincible.
Dogra Barrier.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
You're allowed.
Why? Is the rub-up invincible?
The squeeze is invincible? Is the rubbing invincible?
It's moving, it's peeling off, this
It's stuck.
No, it's falling apart.
That's why it's there.
Crystal Noda's in there right now. I can't move.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, no.
You're a real charmer, Mr. Seta.
Yes, sir.
Well, that's settled.
Because it was already like a mole in that shape, right?
The winner, or rather, the victor is...
Let's have a big round of applause for Sakura Seta!
Wow!
You're number one!
There it is.
There it is, the one you say into the void.
Your reaction is amazing!
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
How was it, Mr. Seta?
It was a game of luck in the end.
Well, but it's part of your skill to draw in the luck, isn't it?
It's wonderful that you are humble enough to say that you were lucky even though you won.
It's wonderful, really.
Amazing.
I knew that fishing leather
I was thinking of doing this.
It's from M-1.
It was the story of M-1.
The part where he was holding back the fishing leather.
The four of us are doing this...
It's good.
So this is what you mean by "character"?
Yes, the characters.
Oh, so this is what a character is?
BKB. BKB
BKB is here
BKB is here.
It's a cat.
Yes, the cat is with Michikura
Mr. Michikura.
Is the cat not Mr. Seta?
Let's start from here.
Yes, Mr. Sasaki.
Let's play!
I wonder if you can convey this to everyone.
I've taken the liberty of asking you to move left and right.
I want you to push the lever on the opposite side.
I want you to be in the middle.
Got it.
Onigiri is awesome!
The outline of the onigiri and the hood are almost the same.
There it is.
There it is!
And, Mr. Dogra, you're doing a pretty good job with the doggies.
Wait a minute.
I see... I can usually tell which side it's swinging to by looking at the tree car on top.
Yes, yes, yes.
If you had a face-removal camera on this, I'd like you to pull a face with the Dogra players right now.
A straight face.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm trying to make a thin, thin, straight face.
Whoa. What's it look like?
Fine, fine.
He's taking the foot.
It doesn't look the same, but all four of you are really good at this.
It's just...
It's not often you get a situation like this.
It's amazing how they all overlap in the center like this.
It's quite painful.
It's like a little train in the middle.
It's amazing, isn't it? It's amazing.
It's amazing how they overlap, really?
Come on, Onigiri-seta, Sakura, you okay?
Dogra-san, you're a real piece of work, aren't you?
Quite.
It's pretty simple.
Uh?
Uh, he's still here.
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on.
They're still here.
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
Ooh-ooh-ooh
And there's a time in the upper right corner.
They're still here.
Pretty much everyone's holding out.
They've been holding for over a minute.
Uh-oh?
They're still here.
Is he gone?
Come on, Seta, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, Setanta.
Seta, you're in the most danger.
He's still here.
How's that?
What?
What's going on?
Prince, prince, you hang in there.
Oh, there he goes.
Which way?
Gone.
Still here. Still here.
Still in front of me, still in front of me.
Ah, here's where Seta dropped out.
He's gone.
The champion of the game just now...
The first one!
Oh no...
I guess this is a game that requires a different ability, isn't it? I guess it's a game that uses different abilities again, this one.
It's so hard!
It's a lot harder than I thought it would be.
It's very difficult.
Yes, it is.
You don't see people doing this for a really long time.
So we don't really promote it as much as we'd like to.
I want everyone to do it.
Oh?
Uh-oh?
Go for it.
Uh-oh. Go for it.
I really want you to experience this.
I just want you to see how great these three of us are doing.
Eh, this is like working until the last person, right? I'm sure it is.
Yes, well, um, well...
Ah!
Oh, oh, there's one, there's one.
Oh, my God!
Now, who's the winner?
What?
Oh, my God!
Four-way tie.
Oh!
Egita's.
Oh, my gosh.
Now, now, oh, oh, oh, me? He was just saying that.
He doesn't even know.
I thought he was out. I thought he was out.
You're drawing the wrong line. He's drawing the wrong picture.
It's true.
Now, so level two was a prince win, but here you go, victory.
I thought we had enough time.
He said he could afford it.
Oh.
I usually train in a heavier gravity.
That's for sure! Indeed!
Yes!
Planet Soldier!
Great, great, great!
No, let's call him "Hattori Soldier" later on when we get mixed up with Mr. Tsuchisaku!
Oh, that's right!
We have the same voice actor.
Me too, I was wondering what I should finally dump on you!
I know, maybe if I say "driven by Seyaka," he'll say it.
You just said it, didn't you?
That's Seyade Drivetrain!
Wow!
Amazing!
No, it's amazing!
You can say that no matter what you shake.
Maybe you don't think I'm Ryu Horikawa.
You're not.
No, it's Vegeta.
Oh, so it's Mr. Vegeta.
Wow.
It's a game where you have to bring more and more food to your mouth so you don't overcook it!
I have to get fat to protect my character.
That's hard work!
So, you mean, I only have to choose what I can eat?
That's right.
There are things you can't eat.
Spam and snot.
I understand.
I'm particular.
I see.
I still don't get it.
I still don't get it
Oh, you're going to grab it and take it with you?
That's not good for the other guy.
Oh, so that's how it is.
You make your Murakami gain weight.
Make the other guy's Murakami lose weight. Make the other guy, Murakami-san, lose weight.
The prince is moving a little.
Prince, you're terrible!
What is it?
Wait a minute.
The prince is in a 4-way.
I don't see any threesomes.
Threesomes.
One's disappearing!
One disappears!
I've lost weight.
One is gone.
Seta has lost weight.
That's great!
You're strong!
You're so strong!
2P Yunosy, you won overwhelmingly.
Good for you, this way.
No, there was someone really bothering me.
Wasn't it a green fork? Wasn't it a green fork?
Green?
Me!
I kept getting non-food things in my mouth too.
No, no!
That's the game in a nutshell.
I see.
I'm not losing weight that fast.
The point is how efficiently you can give what you shouldn't eat to other Murakami.
That's amazing!
Really?
There he is!
Look out, look out!
Weak!
Down there.
Shall I close with this?
Let's close it with this? Let's close with this, shall we?
I see.
Let's close with this, shall we?
This is Mr. Yunosy, right?
Mr. Dokla, right?
Yes, sir.
It's good to wake up.
The song stands naturally and widely.
You came to Takahashi Meiji for this.
It's true, isn't it?
[Hajime Shacho ending]
I can see it! I can see it!
I can see the numbers!
Maesan: "Huh?
Now, Odd!
Mr. Maesan: "Wait a minute! Isn't the prince early?
Prince is early!
Mr. Maesan: "He's so fast!
Mr. Maesan: "And, Mr. Setto, you need to be more serious!
I mean, 15 seconds...
Maesan: "Please be more serious!
Maesan: "Awww..."
10 seconds! Last 10 seconds!
8!
Maesan: "Oh, great, great, great! Prince is amazing! Seriously, that was amazing!
5!
Mr. Maesan: "This is really great!"
2!
1!
Mr. Maesan: "On your finger... what's that on your finger?"
Gather the wood!
Wow! Look, look, look!
Oh, that pose!
That pose! Something's got me!
What was that? When something gets me!
It's not coming out!
You don't know what this is? You know, when you use up all your energy
When you use up all your energy? The one when you use up all your energy?
Maesan: "Yeah, it's too scary!"
Mr.: "Yeah, but it's so fast!"
Of course!
Mr. Maesan: "Is this it?
That's it!
I'm going down the middle!
In the middle!
Go for the middle line and do these two at once.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa...
How did you do it, Mr. Seta?
How did you do it?
I did this while making a circle around these four buttons.
I see.
No, it's not like that. It's like a massage.
Oh, really!
Yes, like that.
Gently!
If you press like this...
I thought it would be a good connection.
Oh, I mean...
You didn't respond.
No, I thought it was funny to see the form of a man who lives at night.
Where is it!
I was a little taken back
So, Mr. Seta, let's surpass ourselves next time
Let's try to surpass 121 times.
Understood, sir.
Another 30 seconds.
Not again!
Let's go for 20 seconds.
Ten seconds.
Short term.
Let's do it.
There's a star in it.
Okay. - Okay. All right.
Good luck.
GO.
What? That was fast!
What?
Mr. Seta, what happened?
Who's Mr. Seta?
Mr. Seta!
Mr. Seta, what happened?
What's going on?
Wait a minute.
Seta... seta...
Seta!
Hey!
Hey, come on!
Your true self, now!
You unleashed your true self!
Hey!
Seta!
You unleashed your true self!
Oh!
Seta!
What's going on?
What happened? What happened?
Se... se...
What is it? Sense?
Sense?
What did you make?
What the fuck?
You didn't even try to act natural.
I thought I had you beat, but now...
No, it's all about stamina.
The second half of the race was completely different.
You're sweating like a pig.
You're sweating like a pig. You're sweating a lot.
Of course he's sweating.
It looks super awesome.
Oh, my God.
Did you use the marine stuff?
Yeah, I think so.
That's not the only case.
That video was really great.
It was 10 times more oceanic.
Up until about 3 seconds before it started.
I was like, "What are you going to do?
It's already started.
I've learned a lot.
I knew it.
You've got a lot of mastery.
That's why I like games so much.
You know, people who hate to lose are more likely to...
Many people like games more than others.
That's true.
I think I caught a glimpse of you.
That's wonderful.
Wonderful.
Everyone in the front.
Yes, thank you very much.
Hot! This game.
It's pretty hot.
It's so hot.
I'm sweating too, even though I'm not playing.
Let's hear a few words from each of you.
Let's start with a word from each of you.
Oh, no, no, no.
Mr. Vegeta.
Vegeta.
I'm sorry.
You've only been here an hour.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
You're here. It was a game. You're here. It was a game.
Woohoo!
Done.
No, nothing's wrong.
It's decided.
Nothing's wrong.
We're in town.
Thank you very much.
Next, Mr. Tsukazakura.
Yes, it was some kind of game.
I was very happy to play games with people I really like and who are professionals.
It was a lot of fun. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your wonderful performance in the end.
I think I used it in the most correct way.
Mr. Hiroba, please. I'm not tired at all because I haven't played at all.
I'm not tired at all, but I had a lot of fun, and I hope to be more active next time.
Thank you very much for having a good time with us.
Thank you very much.
It was so bad, but what kind of tension was it? I was playing this. I was really playing the whole thing... alone.
Alone I realized today that this is the right way to play, and it was fun, thank you very much.
You should definitely request information on ballpoint penji courses. It's true, you can use your time more profitably.
It's a different thing, I think I'm qualified.
I hope this is a good opportunity for you guys to play with it. Thank you very much.
That's the only way to sum it up.
There was a last boss. I can't say that.
That's the only thing I can say that sums it up.
Here you go. You can wear them. Bye-bye. Thank you very much.
I thought you said they were energy potions.
I forgot to tell you... you came all the way out here.
I was wondering if there's going to be a Google channel this time.
We'd love to have you on our Google channel.
It's at 4:30 p.m. on the lawn.
There'll probably be some earthlings in T-shirts hanging around.
So, please have a haircut by this person.
Please come and visit us.
Thank you very much.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Okay, I'll take some.
Three, two, one.
Okay, I'll take a few.
I want to see the admins.
Last one.
I'm gonna hit Trax.
Trax's.
Three, two, one.
Thank you.
You're turning into a boy.
I've never seen that before.
That's amazing.
You listen to rap music, too, right?
This or Trax.
Oh, yeah!
How was the game?
It was nerve-wracking.
I think the seven games
I feel like I blew it.
Thank you very much.
I'm up.
Thank you for teaching me.
Just in time.
My...
I wanted to come over there like this.
But I couldn't because of this thing on my shoulder.
That's too bad.
You're cool to the end.
Thanks, man.
When did you get here?
I don't know.
APEX, FPS.
CALL OF DUTY...
But I also play a lot of other things.
You play a lot of games these days. You've been playing a lot of games lately.
But seriously.
I've only played up to 1 or 2 gaming games.
I'm not at all.
I'm looking for a higher level.
Like this.
Okay.
Thank you for watching.
It went up!
Yes, sir.
I'm gonna get some.
Don't follow me, you guys.
Hey, Uncle Vova!
Shut up!
Vegeta!
Vegeta.
I don't know if you know me.
Vegeta
Thank you.
Mom, let's explain it too.
So the song.
When the number of collapses moves to the first,
The biggest turn from now on,
the most sure place will appear.
The touch play of the sea,
I am not the only one who can do it, but it seems to be able to be calibrated for 2 hours.
Let's go for the fried skewers!
Even if you don't want to burn, everyone!
Thanks irritable
Soga Soga
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
And this too, please.
And this one, please.
Maybe when I'm persistent.
Okay, here we go.
Thank you very much.
You're getting a lot of responses.
Well, thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
I want to take a footbath again.
That felt really good.
How was the footbath?
It was warm.
It was great.
I want to go back.
I want to come back tomorrow if I get a chance.
I'd love to.
By the way, do you two like hot springs?
Yes, we do.
A lot.
Aya has a particular image of them.
My family and my mother all like them.
Whenever I'm in Oita, I'll go to a hot spring and go home.
If I'm in Oita, I'll definitely go home after taking a hot spring bath.
If you see her the day after a concert
I often tell her that I went to the hot spring after the concert.
They often talk about it.
Isn't there a hot spring in Murakata?
There's Yamatsubasa.
It's pretty nice there too.
It's really nice.
I haven't been there yet.
I've never been there. I've never been.
To a hot spring?
Yes, I have.
There are all kinds of baths.
Some inside, some outside.
There's a sauna.
It's great.
The food is good, too.
I see.
Come again sometime.
Thank you very much.
They've arrived.
He's so cute.
Amazing.
Can I tell you a story?
What did you draw?
Did you draw a giraffe?
A yellow one.
You painted a yellow picture?
It was fun.
It was fun, it was fun, it was good, it was good.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
He painted me a yellow picture.
He's so cute.
Bye bye.
They're all a little dirty, but they're cute in that way, too.
Thank you so much!
What kind of picture did you draw?
I drew Anpanman.
You like Anpanman?
I do! It's cute.
Pink? You like pink?
I love it! Like!
Together! Thank you.
Will you continue to draw?
I hope you draw a lot.
Thank you.
I'm a little nervous.
It's been a while.
It's been a while since I've done any additional work.
I haven't used it since middle school.
I didn't use it in high school.
Here we go.
If I draw this keep, doesn't it look like that?
Is that it?
Oh, it's so cute.
It's a pin that makes everyone's heart happy.
Okay, I'll draw a little...
I'm going to draw a little.
Interesting.
Isn't it nice?
Wow!
Nice.
It's nice, it's like... the strokes are big...
It looks like a star.
A lot of love.
I don't know, the dark ones, they're kind of, like, gnarly, you know?
It's like a gnomeo.
It's like a big painting.
Cute.
Is it?
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's put a little bit on the edge.
If no one erases it, it'll stay.
Can you reach it? Miyu-chan, up there.
I can reach it.
It's big.
It's big, isn't it?
It's big, isn't it? It's big.
Can you reach it?
Can you get it?
It's coming. It's coming.
You're right. No one wrote anything down.
It's on the second floor.
Oh, my God.
Two floors above the city.
Do you see the heart coin?
So cute.
Hearts.
Cute.
You're right. If I put a little girl there, she won't be able to reach the sub-miles.
Or tired.
They can reach it, so...
Flowers
Cute.
A cute little girl arrived.
Her name is Hina.
Hina's so cute!
So it's done!
There were lots of them.
Flowers and the sun.
The sun.
It's so cute.
I bought it because it's from the sea and it's natural.
It's cute.
It's amazing.
Liloa put hearts and ears on the hinnya and it looks like a bunny.
Thank you.
I drew a big star in addition to the heart.
I also drew a small cat.
No face.
I drew a cat without a face.
Tomorrow, I would like to evolve this picture by adding sea creatures with Posca.
I will use Posca here. It's this Posca.
The colors are good.
I'm going to paint it.
I would like to depict the beautiful sea that has been restored by your hands.
I would like to paint the story of the creatures coming one after another.
Yes, everyone, please join us tomorrow.
And look forward to the completion!
Enjoy!
Thank you very much!
You want to put this wherever you want?
Yes!
It's empty, so the top is...
It's so empty up there... what do you want me to take?
I take pictures of what I like.
Yes!
Chocolate chip cookies.
It says "not so casual.
If you're looking for a place to buy snacks, have a cup of tea somewhere.
Did you have any snacks?
Buy casually
casually, very casually, very casually
This is just a normal arrangement.
Let's buy a cat, too. I met a cat today.
Thank you very much.
Please go buy one.
Thank you.
Good boy.
Nope.
Uhhh сейчас
Here is a video about the life of a beef carrot!
If you like meat, please subscribe to our channel and check it out!
Overall, SAGE's channel is introduced
The class of a pro-wrestler
European Wrestler's Lesson
Lessons from a Professional Wrestler
Good evening everyone. We are the Battention Women's Squad. Good evening, everyone. We are the Battenington Girls Squad.
Hello!
Nice to meet you.
What are we going to do now, Ai-chan? Please give the title call.
Yes. Let's dance together! The Searching Dance!
Yeah!
Let's dance!
We, the Battension Girls have a very fun song called "Searching for Something",
We have a very fun song called "Searching for Something",
We are going to dance to the song together with the audience.
We are planning to dance it together with the audience.
Safe and sound!
ubenn
me
Swan
I am going to open a Kabi no Mai from now on, please dance with me.
Please dance with me.
I'm going to practice this one, is that OK?
Yes.
I'm going to open the dance with Mr. Fujimoto.
Is this a microphone?
Yes.
Please do.
We haven't practiced yet.
We're practicing now.
That first step looked really difficult.
That's all right.
It's just the chorus.
So this is how it appears.
Let's do this one together.
The first one.
First.
Hands on one, extend up.
This is easy to understand.
Now jump up and down.
Then, next, make your hand like a penguin.
One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four.
Then squat down with your hands circling each other.
How is it? Do you think you can do it?
Let's do it.
Have fun. If you are willing to do it.
Also, if you have young children, you are welcome to go on stage.
If you have young children, please let us know.
Please bring your little friends.
Bigger children should stay where they are.
On the stage.
That's fine. If you like.
Thank you.
Are you a Vashon fan?
Can you hold a penlight?
And your parents, too, if you have them.
Okay, Ishiko, you're coming with me.
And a cell phone light. It's so beautiful.
You should put the mic down.
It's so beautiful.
It's nice.
Thank you very much.
It's different from the tylium.
Music start!
Pure future, innocent dreams, take me with you
(Riding on that wind, these hands and feet flying, towards the birds)
(To the sky, excuse me from above) (To the sky, excuse me from above)
Let's go on a trip! Ready, set, go!
(Ride on the river)
(Tete-tete-tete... (Tete-tete-tete... (I think he's going to dissect it...)
♪ Knock, knock, knock, knock, zero repeats, smile, smile, smile, smile
♪ Knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock, knock.
Let's go find him.
Don't go away again.
Yeah! Thank you!
Thank you!
Thank you! That's great!
Soap bubbles are awesome!
Thank you! Thank you!
How was the dance?
It was fun!
Did you have fun? It was good!
How'd you do? Did you have fun?
It was fun!
Please keep the calls down!
Did you have fun?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're so cute.
It was a great memory.
You guys did a great job.
Thank you.
I was struggling to keep up with you.
So, that's it.
It's already the end of the second day!
So fast!
A lot has happened today.
How was it? Akira.
It was a lot of fun.
I didn't expect it to be this exciting.
I should go home.
This whole day just flew by.
And the live show, too.
And I got to touch a lot of little kids.
And he worked so hard on his giant artwork.
I was so happy.
How was it?
Thank you very much.
I had a great time with you all.
I had a great time talking with you.
Thank you very much.
I had a great time.
Thank you for having me.Sorry to have disturbed you.
You're very good at what you do.
I have been in contact with you for a long time.
Everyone at APA, with whom I had been in contact for some time
It was a footbath
It was a place for healing
and also a place for socializing.
Tomorrow, all the students
will actually come to the event.
I feel very rewarded
I think it's going to be a very rewarding experience.
I think it's going to be a wonderful place
I'm looking forward to it even more.
Thank you very much.
What do you think? I hope you enjoyed it as much as I did.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
It's been a lot of fun.
Thank you all for staying with us this far.
Thank you very much.
We hope to see you again tomorrow!
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
I'm here, so I'll be somewhere else.
Oh, I see.
Thank you very much.
Three, two, one.
Oh!
Is it like this?
It is!
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
That's great, that's great, that's great!
Wonder!
Okay, three, two, one.
Okay, thank you very much.Yes, thank you.
Drawcobble. I've been banging on this all day.
You're not a punching machine.
Fusion!
Special badge.